

Lucy Shepherd

Profile

Friendly and bubbly professional with 15+ years of experience in customer service. Proficient with computers and fast to learn new software and systems. Thrive working in a collaborative team environment or independently. Recent experience includes relationship building with partners and suppliers, technical troubleshooting, creating new website listings for products, managing a large amount of emails and phone calls, and adapting to last minute changes in a fast-paced environment.

Employment History

Product Coordinator/Reservations Agent at ClubConnect

June 2022- Present

Product Coordinator Duties:

- Supplier onboarding
- Commission negotiation
- Supplier communication
- Product listing updates and creation
- API mapping (Using company software)
- Troubleshooting and issue resolution
- Inventory management
- Data tracking (Excel/Spreadsheets)
- MS Office Suite proficiency
- Software utilisation
- Relationship building
- Quickly adapting to last-minute changes

Reservations Agent Duties:

- Inbound and outbound calls
- Email correspondence
- Supplier communication (Bookings, Confirmations, Cancellations)
- Refunds processing
- Fraud management and investigation
- Payment processing
- Customer service
- Fast typing (100+ WPM)
- Complaint handling

Cover Review Consultant at Bupa, Melbourne Team (working from home)

Aug 2021- January 2022

- Customer service
- Product knowledge
- Learning and utilising multiple programs to assist customers

Details

0416 926 664 lucyshepherd@live.com.au

Skills

Customer Service

Communication

Problem Solving

Relationship Building

Technical Proficiency

- Complaint handling
- Completing legal compliance on every interaction
- Explaining health insurance to people from all backgrounds
- Meeting and exceeding KPI's
- Accurately documenting customer interactions
- Creating and sharing cheat-sheets with my team on different subjects

Outbound Telemarketing at Australian Star Services, Gold Coast

April 2021- Aug 2021

- Cold calling
- Building rapport
- Objection handling
- Lead generating
- Reaching and exceeding KPI's
- Data entry

Brand Ambassador at Samsung, Gold Coast

May 2014 — April 2017

- Customer service
- Building rapport with customers and sales staff
- Demonstrating and describing functions of big ticket home appliances including luxury fridges and washing machines
- Closing sales and exceeding KPIs
- Training staff on new products and ensuring up-to-date knowledge
- Basic merchandising / Dressing end caps

Team member at Woolworths, Perth & Port Hedland

May 2010 — October 2012

- Customer service
- Cash handling and EFTPOS
- Building and maintaining displays
- Stock rotation and control
- Ticketing
- · Working across different departments as needed
- Cash office duties including payroll, cash handling, end of day till balancing

Cashier and Customer Service at Domayne, Perth

May 2011 — August 2011

Bakery manager at Woolworths, Perth

August 2008 — February 2010

Education

April 2004

Year 12, Southern Cross Homeschool Academy

February 2011

Certificate III in Fitness, Central Institute of Technology